- Hey.
So, uh, did everything go
okay with the annulment?
Oh, yeah, no problems.
It's all taken care of.
- Ross, thank you.
- Ah.
[both chuckling]
Hey, do you guys
wanna go see a movie?
- Oh, yeah. Why not?
- I'm gonna get my sweater.
Okay.
You want, you want
to hear something weird?
Always.
I didn't get
the annulment.
- What?
- We're still married.
Don't tell Rachel.
See you later.
- Hey, do you have any gum?
- Oh, yeah.
Wait! Wait! Hi.
Listen, Ross, can I just talk
to you for just a second?
Oh, but, Phoebe, we're
gonna be late for the movie.
Oh, there's a cab! Taxi!
Oh, that's lucky, huh?
What timing. My God, huh?
There you go. There you go.
We're-we're actually just
gonna walk 'cause it's
right up there
at the Angelika.
Oh, the Angelika!
Go! Go!
You didn't get
the annulment?
I know.
- Ross?
- Well, I tried.
But when I got to
my lawyer's office
all I could hear
was "Three divorces!"
"Three divorces!"
Look, I just don't
want my tombstone
to read "Ross Geller,
three divorces."
Don't be worried about that.
Your tombstone can say
whatever you want it to say.
It can say, "Ross Geller,
good at marriage."
You know? Mine's gonna say,
"Phoebe Buffay, buried alive."
Look, all I know
is, I, I can't
have another
failed marriage.
So, okay, what, you're
gonna be married to a girl
who doesn't even
know about it.
Oh, woman! Sorry.
Well, okay, so I don't have
it all worked out quite yet.
Just don't, don't say
anything to Rachel, please.
Rachel is one of my
closest friends.
Although, being the only
one that knows about this
does make me
feel special. Okay.
Okay, stop, stop, stop!
- Phoebe!
- Hey, Rach!
What was that?
Sorry. Mix-up.
Hey, how was the movie?
I haven't seen it yet. Ross.
Then you better hurry.
The Angelika! Go! Go!
[shouting]
No!
[theme music]
♪ So no one told you
life was gonna be this way ♪
♪ Your job's a joke
you're broke ♪
♪ Your love life's DOA ♪
♪ It's like you're always
stuck in second gear ♪
♪ When it hasn't been your day
your week your month ♪
♪ Or even your year ♪
♪ But I'll be there for you ♪
♪ 'Cause you're
there for me too-o-o ♪♪
[instrumental music]
You know, when we
move in together
can I get
a gumball machine?
Of course. Joey wouldn't
let you have one?
No. When it comes to sweets,
he's surprisingly strict.
Hey, have you figured out a way
to tell him you're moving out?
No, no, I keep
trying, you know
and I can get out
"Joey, I have to"
but then I lose my nerve
and I always finish with
"Go to the bathroom."
He may think I'm sick.
You know, I really have
to tell Rachel, but I..
We just got to
get it over with.
You know what,
the next time we see them
we're just gonna tell
'em, okay? That's it.
Oh, is that how this
is gonna work now?
You're just gonna
order me around
all the time?
- Pretty much.
- Alright.
- Hey, Monica.
- 'Hi.'
Hey, man, you feeling better?
Yeah, I'm , I'm, uh..
Um, Joey.
We have something
to tell you.
Oh, my God!
You're pregnant!
- No. No.
- No.
[chuckles]
No.
Look, Joe,
here's the thing.
Um..
...Monica and I have decided
to live together, here.
So..
...I'm gonna be
moving out, man.
Wow.
Well, uh, hey.
I'm really happy for you
guys. Congratulations.
- See you later.
- Hey, Joey, Joey.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah. I gotta go.
I've got an acting job.
Like you'd
believe that.
This sucks!
Look, I'm-I'm just gonna
be right across the hall
and I promise you, the minute
Monica and I break up
I'm moving right
back in with you.
Okay, look,
look, look, uh..
...if you're gonna
be moving in with him
I feel that it is
my responsibility
to tell you the truth
about him, okay?
He's a terrible
roommate. Terrible!
He, uh, forgets to, um..
...he, uh, oh, always,
he always, uh..
Oh, who am I kiddin'?
He's the best roommate ever!
[upbeat music]
- Hey, Pheebs.
- Hey.
Hey, have you
seen Rachel?
- No. Why?
- I have some exciting news.
[gasps]
You're pregnant.
No!
Chandler and I are
moving in together.
Ooh, that's good. Wow.
But now, if you were pregnant
what would you name it?
Hint, Phoebe.
- Hey.
- What's up?
- Well, um..
Chandler and I are
moving in together.
Oh, my God.
Oh-h-h, my little sister
and my best friend
shackin' up.
Well, that's great.
That's great. Come here. Muah!
- You guys, I'm happy too.
- Okay, come here.
Wow, big day, huh?
People moving in,
people getting annulled.
Anyway, I gotta go find Rachel,
but, um, if you guys see her
would you please try to give
her some really bad news
so mine doesn't seem so bad.
- Okay.
- Okay. Bye.
Hmm, something
bad to tell Rachel.
Bad news for Rachel.
What could that be?
Can you just, can you
just lay off, please?
Alright. My life
is an embarrassment.
I should just go live
under somebody's stairs.
Ross, it's not that big a deal.
So, you'll have been
divorced three times.
You'll still have a life.
You'll go on dates.
No. No. No, I won't.
I'll be at the bottom
of the dating barrel now.
Alright, the only guys below
me will be four-divorce guy
uh...murderer guy
and-and geologists.
[chuckles]
Ross, you're being
ridiculous, okay?
You are cute and smart and sweet
and that is much more important
than three stupid divorces.
Oh, yeah, have you
ever dated anyone
who's been divorced three times?
Well, that's not
really fair, you know.
Most guys who've been
divorced three times
are like 60.
Ross, nobody cares
about this except you.
You, uh, this embarrassment
thing is all in your head.
Here, I'll show you.
- Come here.
- What?
Hi! Hi. Listen.
My friend Ross is
about to be divorced
for the third time,
but wouldn't you date him?
And if you
wait right here
I'll go get Ross.
[door opens]
- Hi.
- Oh!
I thought you were Rachel.
What gave me away?
I just got to tell her.
I have to get it over with.
I've told Ross and Phoebe
and she's the only one left.
Okay, that's it,
so everybody knows.
It's official,
we're moving in together.
No turning back.
[growling]
Are you scared? Are you?
- No.
- That was my scariest voice.
You're very brave.
- Hey.
Ugh! The worst day.
You know, you think you're
finally making progress at work
and then your boss
calls you Raquel.
Uh, hey, listen, for the first
four years of my work
everybody called
me Cha-la-la.
- Seriously.
- I believe you.
So, it was right in
the middle of a staff meeting.
So, of course, no one
else wants to correct her.
So everyone else
is calling me Raquel.
By the end of the day
the mailroom guys
were calling me Rocky.
Well, I-I still think
you're very, very nice
and very pretty.
What?
All yours, babe.
Rachel..
Have a seat.
Okay, listen, um..
...Chandler and I..
...are going
to live together.
Here.
Oh, my God.
That's so great!
Oh! I'm so happy
for you guys!
- Really?
- Oh!
And that was so
sweet of you to ask.
[gasps]
Oh, my God!
The three of us
are gonna have such
a good time living together!
[gasps]
Yes, we are.
Oh, and, Chandler,
you're gonna have to watch
those long showers
you take in the morning
'cause you know
Raquel can't be late.
- Rach.
- Yeah, he's gonna work on that.
Oh. Oh! This is so exciting.
Oh, wow.
[gasps]
♪ Come and knock on our door ♪
♪ We'll be waiting for you ♪
[instrumental music]
See? Once you know
the stories, it's not that bad.
First marriage,
wife's hidden sexuality
not my fault.
Second marriage, said
the wrong name at the altar
a little my fault.
Third marriage, well,
they really shouldn't
allow you to get married
when you're that drunk
and have writing all over
your face, Nevada's fault.
Okay, so what do
you think, ladies?
Who wouldn't be interested?
Who wouldn't want to date him?
Well, the divorces
don't bother me.
I'd date him, but not
while he's still married.
Okay, what about you?
Wouldn't you want a date?
Actually, I'm not
dating at all anymore.
See, I figured out that
I was only dating guys
that were, you know,
like, bad for me.
So, I decided that until
I could work that out--
Good, good, whatever.
'What about you, Meg?'
Well, I don't care
about the divorces either
but I wouldn't date him.
It's just that he's obviously
still in love with
this Rachel girl.
What?
She said, "He's obviously
still in love with.."
[indistinct whispering]
This is crazy.
I mean, yes, yes.
Rachel is my good friend
and I, I have
loved her in the past
but now she
is just my wife.
Phoebe, will you, will
you help me out here?
Well, I thought you loved her
when you, when you married her.
We were drunk.
I would have married, uh, Joey
with that amount of alcohol.
Hey! You could do a lot
worse than Joey Tribbiani.
Look, I'm sorry,
but you guys are wrong.
I just don't wanna
be divorced three times.
Yes, and now he's using
this three-divorces reason
because he wants
to stay married to her
because he loves her.
I must say, well done.
Bravo, Meg.
Okay, fine, fine.
If this what you
think, forget about
the whole three-divorce
thing, okay?
I-I'll go to my
lawyer's office right now
and get this
marriage annulled, okay?
She means nothing to me. Noth..
Nothing!
Okay, now I
wouldn't date you
because you seem
a little creepy.
I am so attracted
to him right now.
[instrumental music]
Okay, when are we
gonna tell Rachel
what actually is
going to happen?
Soon. I just
couldn't before.
I mean, you saw
how upset Joey got.
I couldn't do that to her,
she's my best friend.
Well, Joey's
my best friend.
I'm not your best friend?
You just said..
You know, uh..
Of course, you're
my best friend.
Would you please
tell Rachel, though?
Alright. Alright,
at least I'm prepared.
Okay.
- Oh, yes.
- Hey!
Hey, hey.
These aren't for you.
Are you upset?
I am now.
Hey, roomie.
Okay, bye.
Rach?
There's something, uh...
important I have to tell you.
[gasps]
Are you pregnant?
[sighs]
No, but I'm throwing
this shirt away.
I think there was a little,
uh, misunderstanding before.
Um, when I said that, uh,
that Chandler and I wanted
to, uh, live together..
...we meant alone together.
[laughing]
Oh! Oh, my God.
Oh, that's funny.
I can't believe I did that.
Oh, no, sweetie.
No, you know what?
This is my fault.
I, I wasn't clear.
I, uh, I'm really sorry.
And-and listen..
...you take as much time as
you need to move out, okay?
There's absolutely
no rush.
Okay.
Don't you want a cookie?
Sure.
Thanks.
Maybe do you need a tissue?
Mm-hmm.
Monica, where
did you get these?
- I made them.
- Oh!
God, they're so yummy.
[sighs]
God, it's
gonna be weird
like when I come home
and you're not here, you know?
No more Joey and Chan's.
No more J and C's.
Wanna go over to
Joey and Chandler's?
Can't. It's not there.
Look, I'm just gonna
be across the hall.
We can still do
all the same stuff.
Yeah, but we won't
be able to like
get up in the middle of
the night and have those
long talks about our
feelings and the future.
Not once did we do that.
- Hi.
- Hey!
So, I...I told Rachel that it's
just gonna be the two of us.
Oh, yeah? Well,
how'd she take it?
Really well, yeah.
Surprisingly well.
Yeah. She-she didn't cry.
She wasn't angry or sad.
And you're upset
because you didn't
make your
best friend cry?
I mean, all I'm asking for
is just a little emotion.
Is that too much to
ask after six years?
And what? Are-are Rachel and I
not as close as you guys?
I mean, do we not
have as much fun?
Don't I deserve a few tears?
And when we told Joey,
he cried his eyes out.
Hey!
I did not cry
my eyes out!
I mean, come on.
It's like the end of an era.
No more J-man and Channy's.
Okay, I got to ask.
Who calls us that?
[instrumental music]
You got married again?
Yes.
So, that's your second
marriage in two years.
Yes. Second in two years.
Third...overall.
Ross, I have been
a divorce attorney
for 23 years
and never have I had
so much business
from one client.
Why don't you tell
me what happened?
Basically, Rachel and I were
in Vegas and we got drunk--
I'm sorry.
Is this the same
Rachel whose name
you said at the altar
in the second marriage?
Yes, yes, yes!
[chuckles]
But I-I do not love her.
Oh.
That's better then.
This was just
a drunken mistake
and I-I need
to get it annulled.
I see. Have you
considered therapy?
I think just
the annulment for today.
There are a couple
of forms to fill out.
Easy.
And we'll need to have witnesses
who can testify that you
were not of sound mind.
[chuckles]
No problem.
And we'll need you and Rachel
to testify before a judge.
Ooh.
There's no way to
do this without her?
'Cause I kind
of already told her
uh, it was, it
was taken care of.
Of course, you did.
Look, Ross, you
can't get an annulment
unless you and Rachel
are both there.
Uh-huh.
What about someone
who looks like Rachel?
I will think
about the therapy.
[instrumental music]
- Hey.
So, um...I was thinking
that maybe we should start
dividing up our stuff.
Okay.
You know, no-no point
in dragging it out.
Dragging out the long
process of you moving out
and us not living
together anymore.
Okay.
Hey, Rach.
- Yeah?
- What about this?
Huh, who-who gets this?
See, I-I don't know if I
want it because, you know
it might be too many memories.
- What the hell is that?
- I don't know.
Hey, Rachel, how
about the big plate?
I want you to have
the big plate.
Wow. Monica, thanks.
I love this plate.
Something to remember me by.
Mon, honey,
you're not dying.
I'm just moving out.
You know, I mean, we're gonna
see each other all the time.
But still...
it's a big change.
The end of an era,
you might say.
Are you okay?
You're not blinking.
I'm fine. I just..
I was thinking about how
it's-it's an end of an era.
Oh, alright.
But you know, I gotta
say, I don't, I don't think
six years
counts as an era.
And era is defined as
a significant period of time.
Now, it was
significant for me.
Maybe it wasn't
significant to you!
What is the matter with you?
Why aren't
you more upset?
Aren't you gonna be sad
that we're, that we're
not living
together anymore?
I mean, aren't you
gonna miss me at all?
Monica, alright.
But don't get mad at me..
It's, it's just
a little hard to believe.
What's hard to believe?
Well, you know,
I mean, it's you guys.
You-you do this kind
of stuff, you know?
I mean, you-you were
gonna get married in Vegas
and then you backed out..
I guess I'm not upset
because I don't see you
actually going through
with it. I'm sorry.
Rachel.
It's going to happen.
Chandler is gonna
move in here.
- But I--
- I know, well, uh..
Just let me finish, okay?
This isn't something
that we just, just
impulsively decided
to do in-in Vegas.
This is something that
we both really want.
And it is going to happen.
It is?
Really?
Yeah, sweetie.
You mean, we're..
...we're not going to
live together anymore?
No.
What?
Oh, my God!
I'm gonna miss
you so much!
I'm gonna miss you!
I mean,
it's the end of an era!
I know!
[instrumental music]
- Okay, bye.
- Oh, no.
So, did you get
the annulment?
- I couldn't.
- I knew it.
Because you love Rachel.
It's not that, okay?
Annulments are more
complicated than I--
Yeah, complicated
'cause of the love.
I, I do, I do
not love Rachel.
I'm gonna tell her right
now about the whole thing
so we can get this
marriage annulled
as fast as
possible, okay?
Would I do that
if-if I loved her?
I've never been more convinced
of your love for her.
I do not have feelings
for Rachel, okay?
Oh, what's wrong?
Monica and Chandler are
really moving in here
and I have to move out
and everything is changing.
Oh, my God, come here.
Come here.
It's okay. Ah.
Everything is gonna be okay.
- Thank you.
- Of course.
[instrumental music]
So, Ross and Rachel
got married.
Monica and Chandler
almost got married.
You think you and I
should hook up?
Oh, we do.
But not just yet.
Really? But when?
Okay, um, ahem, well..
...first Chandler
and Monica will get married
and be filthy rich,
by the way
but, um, it won't work out.
- Wow.
- I know.
Then I'm gonna marry
Chandler for the money
and you'll marry Rachel
and have the beautiful kids.
Great.
But then we ditch those two
and that's when we get married.
We'll have
Chandler's money
and Rachel's kids.
And getting custody will be easy
because of Rachel's
drinking problem.
Oh-oh. What about Ross?
I don't wanna go
into the whole thing
but, um, we have
words and I kill him.
[theme music]